wearfigs.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy– FIGS

******FIGS Privacy Policy**

Welcome to  **www.wearfigs.com**  (the “ **Site** ”), a website operated by FIGS (“ **FIGS** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **us** ”, or “ **our** ”).  If you’re reading this, you know that our Site provides users with an opportunity to learn more about and purchase high quality medical apparel (such apparel, our “ **Products** ”).  We know you are concerned about your privacy, so we developed this privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) to explain how we collect, use, and disclose information from and/or about you, whether you are simply visiting our Site, making a purchase, or otherwise interacting with us.

YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE PROCESSED BY US IN THE COUNTRY WHERE IT WAS COLLECTED AS WELL AS OTHER COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN THE LAWS IN YOUR COUNTRY.  BY USING THIS SITE AND PROVIDING ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE TRANSFER OF DATA FROM YOUR COUNTRY TO A COUNTRY THAT HAS LESS STRINGENT LAWS, AND THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN CONFORMANCE WITH THIS POLICY.

So we are clear about the terminology we are using, when we use the phrase  **“Personal Information”**  in this Privacy Policy, we mean contact information (e.g., name, address, email address, or telephone number) and any other information that can be used to personally identify an individual.

**Children.**

The Site is not directed to children and children are not eligible to use our Site.  Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us.  We do not collect or maintain Personal Information from people we actually know are under 13 years of age, and no part of our Site is designed to attract people under 13 years of age. When the Site does collect age information, and users identify themselves as under 13, we will take steps to remove that user's Personal Information from our databases and to prevent the user from utilizing the Site. Additionally, if you are under the age of majority (typically 18 or 19 years, depending on your jurisdiction), you may not purchase any Products.

**How We Collect and Use Personal Information.  **

We may collect Personal Information when you:

  * Create an Account through our Site
  * Make a purchase
  * Sign-up to receive marketing communications
  * Enter a contest or participate in a promotion
  * Contact us with a comment, question or complaint
  * Participate in a survey or customer research
  * Apply to or participate in our Ambassador Program

_Create an Account_ **:** You do not have to create an account in order to browse our Site or place an order. If you choose to create an account, we will collect your first and last name, email address and password in order to create and administer your account. We strongly recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in any unsolicited communication (such as letters, phone calls or email messages).

_Purchases_ **:** To place an order, we will require your first and last name, email address, mailing address, billing address and phone number. We collect this information to process, fulfill and deliver your order of Products, including to process your payment.

_Marketing Communications_ : If you subscribe to our email mailing list, we collect your name and email address as well as other information on an optional basis to help us tailor our communications to you. You can opt out of receiving marketing communications from the Site such as our newsletter by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each email or emailing us at [stat@wearfigs.com](mailto:stat@wearfigs.com). Please note that even if you unsubscribe or opt-out, we may still send you transactional, order, Site and Product related communications (e.g., emails related to your orders or comments). 

_Contests and Promotions_ **:** When you enter a contest or participate in a promotion, we may collect your name, address, email address, phone number, and any additional information or content required for the contest or promotion. We use this information to administer your participation in the contest or promotion, including to deliver a prize to you if you are the winner. These contests and promotions are voluntary.  We recommend that you read the rules for each contest and promotion that you enter.

_Contact Us_ **:** When you contact us with a comment, question or complaint through email, social media or telephone, you may be asked for information that identifies you, such as your name, address and a phone number, along with additional information we need to help us promptly respond to your requests, answer your questions, resolve disputes, and/or troubleshoot problems. We may retain this information to assist you in the future and to improve the quality of our Site, customer service, and Products.

_Surveys and Customer Research_ : From time to time, we may offer you the opportunity to participate in one of our surveys or other customer research. The information obtained through our surveys and customer research is used in an aggregated, non-personally identifiable form. We use this information to help us understand our customers, to improve our Products, Site and promotions.

_Ambassador Program_ : When you apply to or participate in our FIGS Ambassador Program, we may collect your name, address, email address, phone number, job title, social media handles and any additional information or content required for application to or participation in the program. We use this information to evaluate whether you are a good match for our Ambassador Program and to administer the benefits of the program. Applying to and participating in the Ambassador Program is voluntary. 

**Information about our Site.**

  * _Information Collected by Our Servers_.  In general, you can visit our Site without telling us who you are or submitting any Personal Information. However, to make our Site more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) collect information from you, including your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (“ **IP** ”) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), domain name, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit. We use this information to help us understand our Site activity and to monitor and improve our Site.

  * _Log Files._ As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider ( **“ISP”** ), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.  We use this information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users’ movements around the Site, gather demographic information about our user base as a whole, and better tailor our Site to our users’ needs.  For example, some of the information may be collected so that when you visit the Site or again, it will recognize you and the information could then be used to serve advertisements and other information appropriate to your interests. For more information, see the “Interest-Based Advertising” section below.

  * _Cookies_.  Like many online services, we use cookies to collect information.   **“Cookies”** are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the website.  We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site.  This type of information is collected to make the Site more useful to you and to tailor the experience with us to meet your special interests and needs.  

  * _     Third Party Analytics_.  We may use third party tracking and analytics services such as Google Analytics to track and analyze how visitors use our Site. Such third parties may use Cookies to help track user behavior. We do not have access or control over these Cookies. For example, Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the Site, rather than your name or other Personal Information.  We do not combine the information generated through the use of Google Analytics with other Personal Information. Although Google Analytics places a persistent Cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit the Site, the Cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google.  Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Service](https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/analytics/terms/us/) and the [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US). You can prevent the storage of data relating to your use of the Site and created via the cookie (including your IP address) by Google, as well as the processing of this data by Google, by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available at the following link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>. You can also obtain additional information on Google Analytics’ collection and processing of data and data privacy and security at the following link: 
    * <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>; and
    * <https://support.google.com/analytics/topic/2919631>

  * _Third Party Links_ : The Site may contain links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us, including our partner sites and social media websites. We provide links to third party websites as a convenience to the user. These links are not intended as an endorsement of or referral to the linked websites. We have no control over, do not review and are not responsible for the privacy policies of or content displayed on such other websites, and therefore we have no responsibility or liability in any manner for the manner in which the organizations that operate such linked websites may collect, use or disclose, secure or otherwise treat Personal Information. When you click on such a link, you will leave our Site and go to another site.  During this process, another entity may collect Personal Information about you. The linked websites have separate and independent privacy policies, notices and terms of use. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any new website you visit.

**Interest-Based Advertising.**

We work with third parties such as ad networks and other advertising companies that use their own tracking technologies (including cookies and pixel tags) on our Site in order to provide you with tailored advertisements across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your activity on our Site and third-party websites (such as web pages you visit and your interaction with our advertising and other communications) and use this information to make predictions about your preferences, develop personalized content and deliver ads that are more relevant to you on third party websites. This information may also be used to evaluate the effectiveness of our online advertising campaigns.

_Opting-out of Interest-Based Advertising_ : For more information about interest-based advertising and to understand your options, including how you can opt-out of receiving behavioural ads from third-party advertising companies, please visit the Digital Advertising Alliance at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> and the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada website at  <http://youradchoices.ca/choices>.  

Please note that even if you opt-out of interest-based advertising by a third party, these tracking technologies may still collect data for other purposes including analytics and you will still see ads from us, but the ads will not be targeted based on behavioural information about you and may therefore be less relevant to you and your interests.

To successfully opt out, you must have cookies enabled in your web browser (see your browser’s instructions for information on cookies and how to enable them). Your opt-out only applies to the web browser you use so you must opt-out of each web browser on each computer you use. Once you opt out, if you delete your browser’s saved cookies, you will need to opt-out again.

**How We Share Information.**

We may share certain Personal Information in the following circumstances:

  * _Service Providers_ : Your Personal Information may be transferred to third party vendors who help us provide the Site or sell Products to you on our behalf, including vendors that process purchases for us, host the Site, verify your eligibility for a certain discounts, and provide advertising and marketing services. Our service providers are only provided with the information they need to perform their designated functions and are not authorized to use or disclose personal information for their own marketing or other purposes. Our service providers may be located in the U.S., Canada or other foreign jurisdictions.

  * _Affiliates_ : To a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, “ **Affiliates** ”), in the event we have such Affiliates in the future, in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

  * _Legal and Compliance_ : We and our Canadian, U.S. and other foreign service providers may disclose your personal information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (i) resolve disputes, investigate problems, or enforce our Terms of Use; (ii) comply with relevant laws or to respond to requests from law enforcement, regulatory bodies or other government officials relating to investigations or alleged illegal activity, or in response to a subpoena, a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order; (iii) another organization for the purposes of investigating a breach of an agreement or contravention of law or detecting, suppressing or preventing fraud; or (iv) protect and defend our rights or property or the rights and property of you or third parties.

  * _Sale of Business_ : We may transfer any information we have about you as an asset in connection with a proposed or completed merger, acquisition or sale (including transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) involving all or part of FIGS or as part of a corporate reorganization or other change in corporate control.

  * _Social Networking Services:_ Some aspects of our Site may enable you to post content to social networking services (SNSs) such as Facebook, Instagram or Twitter.  If you choose to do this, we will provide information to such SNSs in accordance with your elections and we may also obtain information from SNSs about your interactions with the SNSs.  You acknowledge and agree that you are solely responsible for your use of those websites and that it is your responsibility to review the terms of use and privacy policy of the third party provider of such SNSs.  We will not be responsible or liable for: (i) the availability or accuracy of such SNSs; (ii) the content, products or services on or availability of such SNSs; or (iii) your use of any such SNSs.

  * We may also share Personal Information with third parties to whom you ask us to send Personal Information, or otherwise with your consent.

We may also disclose non-identifiable information publicly without restriction, including to third party vendors who may help us enhance or provide the Site or to third parties. 

**Safeguards and Retention.**

We have implemented reasonable administrative, technical and physical measures in an effort to safeguard the Personal Information in our custody and control against theft, loss and unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure. We restrict access to Personal Information on a need-to-know basis to employees and authorized service providers who require access to fulfil their job requirements.

**Updating, Accessing and Controlling Your Information.**

Subject to applicable law, you have the right to access, update and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information in our custody and control. If you have an account with us, you may update certain of your Personal Information on our Site. You can opt out of receiving marketing communications, including receiving physical mail marketing communications, by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each email or emailing us at [stat@wearfigs.com](mailto:stat@wearfigs.com). You can ask us to delete your information submitted to our Ambassador Program by emailing us at [ambassador@wearfigs.com](mailto:ambassador@wearfigs.com). You may request access to, updating of and corrections of inaccuracies in other of your Personal Information in our custody or control by emailing us at [stat@wearfigs.com](mailto:stat@wearfigs.com). We may request certain Personal Information for the purpose of verifying the identity of the individual seeking access to his or her Personal Information records.

You may request deletion of your Personal Information by us, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete Personal Information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives and we may also retain non-identifiable information about your use of our Site and purchase of Products.  Once we disclose some of your Personal Information to third parties, we cannot access that Personal Information any longer and you will need to contact the third party to request access, deletion or modification of any such information by the parties to whom we have made those disclosures.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy.**

This Privacy Policy is subject to revision from time to time on a going-forward basis.  We will post any revised version of the Privacy Policy on this page.  If we make any material changes to it, we will also send you notice to the last email address you have provided to us.  Continued use of our Site or ordering Products following notice of such changes will indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

**Contact Us.**

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or the manner in which we or our service providers treat your personal information, please contact us at legal@wearfigs.com.

This Policy was last revised: October 4, 2019.
